Hi there. So here I am at Washington Park, New York City. I have no idea if anyone will
show up for my first ever live Coursera office hours held here in New York City. So off we
go. I'm here at Starbucks right outside New York University and we're having our first
office hours and I'm going to have everybody say hi and say hi to all the rest of you.
Hang on. So say hi to everybody. Hello. This is a great pleasure to be starting on the
new road of education with Coursera. This is going to change the future. We expect to
have a lot of fun and intelligence in doing it. Okay. Hi, I'm Jacob and I second what
she said. Okay. Thanks to Dr. Chuck for offering this unique experience and the special office
hours. Okay. Hi, I'm Collette and I'm really enjoying the opportunity to give Paul and
I have some classes with Coursera. Okay. Hi, I'm Tony and I thank you for the opportunity
to study and I look forward to your other courses. Okay, so we're about out of time
here at New York City so we'll see you next week in Los Angeles.